coastal24.com 2012-10-15

# COASTAL - Privacy Form

**Why?**   
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.

**What?**   
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:

  * Social Security number and credit card or other debt
  * account balances and mortgage rates and payments
  * payment history and checking account information  

When you are _no longer_ our member, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.

**How?**   
All financial companies need to share members' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members' personal information; the reasons Coastal Federal Credit Union chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.

**Reasons we can share your personal information** | **Does Coastal Federal Credit Union share?** | **Can you limit this sharing?**  
---|---|---  
**For our everyday business purposes -**   
such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus   
| Yes | No  
**For our marketing purposes -**   
to offer our products and services to you   
| Yes | No  
**For joint marketing with other  
financial companies ** | Yes | No  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -**   
information about your transactions and experiences  | Yes | No  
**For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -**   
information about your creditworthiness  | No | We don't share  
**For nonaffiliates to market to you** | No | We don't share  
  
**Questions?**   
Call toll-free 800-868-4262 or go to www.COASTAL24.com 

**How does Coastal Federal Credit Union protect my personal information?**   
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.   

**How does Coastal Federal Credit Union collect my personal information?**   
We collect your personal information, for example, when you 

  * open an account or deposit money 
  * pay your bills or apply for a loan 
  * use your credit or debit card 

We also collect your personal information on an ongoing basis from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies. 

**Why can't I limit all sharing?**   
Federal law gives you the right to limit only: 

  * sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness 
  * affiliates from using your information to market to you 
  * sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you 

State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.

**Definitions**   
**Affiliates -** Companies related by common ownership or control. They be financial and nonfinancial companies. 

  * _Our affiliates include nonfinancial companies such as Daymark Realty, LLC; Coastal Title, LLC; and Coastal Federal Financial Group, LLC._

**Nonaffiliates -** Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. 

  * _Nonaffiliates we share with can include insurance companies, direct marketing companies and credit card companies._

**Joint Marketing -** A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you. 

  * _Our joint marketing partners include insurance companies and credit card companies._

Rev 6/12
